[
    {
        "question": "Zero",
        "choice1": "seis",
        "choice2": "diez",
        "choice3": "dos",
        "choice4": "cero",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "One",
        "choice1": "cinco",
        "choice2": "nueve",
        "choice3": "uno",
        "choice4": "siete",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Two",
        "choice1": "dos",
        "choice2": "cero",
        "choice3": "diez",
        "choice4": "cuatro",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Three",
        "choice1": "ocho",
        "choice2": "tres",
        "choice3": "dos",
        "choice4": "uno",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Four",
        "choice1": "diez",
        "choice2": "cuatro",
        "choice3": "uno",
        "choice4": "nueve",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Five",
        "choice1": "ocho",
        "choice2": "nueve",
        "choice3": "cinco",
        "choice4": "dos",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Six",
        "choice1": "cinco",
        "choice2": "ocho",
        "choice3": "seis",
        "choice4": "nueve",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Seven",
        "choice1": "siete",
        "choice2": "uno",
        "choice3": "cero",
        "choice4": "nueve",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Eight",
        "choice1": "seis",
        "choice2": "cinco",
        "choice3": "siete",
        "choice4": "ocho",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Nine",
        "choice1": "nueve",
        "choice2": "cero",
        "choice3": "seis",
        "choice4": "ocho",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Ten",
        "choice1": "siete",
        "choice2": "diez",
        "choice3": "dos",
        "choice4": "cuatro",
        "answer": 2
    }
]